- [METAL DOOR CREAKING]
- [CLOCK TICKING]
[CREAKING CONTINUES]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[METAL DOOR OPENING]
[METAL DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
- [TICKING CONTINUES]
- [FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[METAL DOOR OPENS]
PRISON GUARD: Open 15.
- [DOOR LOCK CLICKING]
- [DOOR BUZZING]
[METAL DOOR RUMBLING, OPENING]
- [FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
- [KEYS JANGLING]
[SHEETS RUSTLING]
PRISON GUARD: Hey, get up!
You got a visitor. Look alive.
[DOOR BUZZING]
[METAL DOOR RUMBLING, OPENING]
Becket.
I'm Father James Morris,
one of the chaplains here.
How are you feeling today?
[BECKET GRUNTS SOFTLY]
Cheesecake?
No, thank you.
BECKET: You know,
I ordered vanilla
and they brought me chocolate.
Kill me now.
So, Father, appreciate you
coming down here,
but I'm fine.
Well, forgive me,
but most people
in your position
feel a bit differently.
Well, I'd argue
most people in my position,
most people, in general,
lack my sense of clarity,
presence of mind.
FATHER MORRIS:
I don't mean to overstep,
but, um, this may be
the last opportunity
you have to speak to anyone.
Is there nothing
you'd like to share?
[TICKING CONTINUES]
BECKET: You know
why I'm here, right?
- I know a little.
- BECKET: Well, it's not true.
The real story,
it's much more...
impressive.
Well, you want
to tell me about it?
Well...
I should warn you...
it's a tragedy.
And it doesn't even
start with me.
Funny enough,
it starts with someone else.
And by that I mean, my mother.
...has completely
forgotten how to play.
...Mary Estella Redfellow.
Longtime resident
of Huntington, Long Island,
an heiress to a family fortune
valued then at 18,
19 billion US dollars.
- Thank you.
- [INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
BECKET: Now,
there's a rumor out there
that money
doesn't buy happiness.
Dead wrong.
Money does buy happiness.
We're all adults here.
Let's move on.
[SOFT INSTRUMENTAL
MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm told that the night
she met my father
was a night like any other.
And by that, I mean
she was young, rich.
What could ever go wrong?
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
- MARY: What time is it?
- [COW MOOING]
MARY: Oh, my God!
- CELLIST: What?
- Oh, my God,
- I have to go right now.
- You gotta go now?
MARY: Bye.
[LAUGHING] What are you doing?
- MARY: I have to go.
- Okay.
MAN: I applaud you
for telling us.
That being said,
I think you know
what has to happen.
I'm 18.
Tragically.
No.
This should be my decision.
This should be me.
All right.
You can either get rid of it
or do what you like.
But not here.
Not under this roof.
[SIGHS SOFTLY]
BECKET: In this way, she went
from being Mary Redfellow
of Huntington, New York...
[VEHICLES RUSHING]
...to Mary Redfellow
- of Belleville, New Jersey.
- [TRUCK HORN BLOWS]
- [SCREAMING]
- [DOCTOR MURMURING]
DOCTOR: Breathe.
- [SCREAMING CONTINUES]
- [OBJECTS CLATTERING]
DOCTOR: You're doing well.
Breathe.
MARY: I can't. No, no.
BECKET My father saw me
only once...
- CELLIST: Oh, my God!
- [OBJECTS CLATTERING]
...which was enough to give
him a pulmonary embolism
right there at Jersey City
Memorial Hospital.
...a vehicle that we haven't
seen before...
BECKET: My mother
was left alone
to work at the Newark
Department of Motor Vehicles.
- [TELEPHONE RINGING]
- [INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
Pretty soon, she told me
something important.
MARY: In the painting...
BECKET: We may have been
kicked out of the family,
but we weren't kicked
out of the inheritance.
See, my grandfather had
drawn up an irrevocable trust
to avoid paying estate taxes.
It meant that the fortune,
the whole thing,
the real estate,
the boats, the planes,
an island or two,
would be passed down
to the next oldest in line,
no matter what.
And me, being the youngest,
I might inherit
the entire thing someday,
assuming I outlive the others.
[MARY SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
BECKET: I just had to wait.
For all of them to die.
- [TICKING CONTINUES]
- [DOOR BUZZING]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
BECKET: Now a single mother
doing it all herself,
you might assume
- life was tough, but...
- [DOG BARKING]
...I'll tell you now...
MARY: 'Cause they all sound
the same once you...
...despite our
financial handicap,
she made sure I had all
the culture, class, and style
of a highborn young man.
So when it goes,
it goes through the target.
See how much
of a difference that makes?
- YOUNG BECKET: Mmm-hmm.
- See?
You just open up your shoulders.
That is so much better.
Okay.
BECKET: That was
the first time...
the first time I saw her.
Julia Steinway.
Right off, I could see
we were the perfect match.
- [CHILDREN EXCLAIMING]
- And clearly, I wasn't wrong.
This was, without a doubt,
a girl of great
social bearing, taste, charm.
JULIA'S MOTHER: What's next?
The big one?
[HORSE WHINNIES]
BECKET: I was
in the right place.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
What are you doing here?
Your mom invited me.
Where do you live?
Belleville Township.
Do you live on the street?
What?
YOUNG JULIA: I heard people
there live on the street.
I don't live on the street.
And I mean, I won't
be there forever
because I'm supposed to inherit
a lot of money
or something, so...
YOUNG JULIA:
A lot of money, huh?
Are you trying to impress me?
It's okay if you are.
[SOFT PIANO MUSIC PLAYING]
[AUDIENCE APPLAUDING]
PIANO TEACHER:
Next, we have Lyle Archdale!
[HIGH-TEMPO
PIANO MUSIC PLAYING]
[DISTANT THUNDER RUMBLING]
[ELECTRICAL BUZZING]
- [PIANO MUSIC STOPS]
- [AUDIENCE MURMURING]
PIANO TEACHER: It's all right.
Everyone, it's okay.
Lyle, can you see?
Just keep playing.
[YOUNG BECKET INHALES SHARPLY]
[PIANO MUSIC RESUMES]
[ELECTRICAL BUZZING]
[PIANO MUSIC FADES]
DOCTOR: Hey, Becket.
Can you come with me?
BECKET:
Well, my mother was young...
which is why
she hadn't paid attention
to the symptoms at first.
- Doctors either.
- [CLOCK TICKING]
And the family, um,
I'm sure they knew.
I'm sure they could've helped.
But nothing.
Not one single word.
MARY: Becket,
this is all wrong.
YOUNG BECKET:
What's all wrong?
You should have more than this.
Something was taken from you.
And I want you
to promise me something.
Will you do that?
Okay.
MARY: Promise me...
that you won't quit...
until you have
the right kind of life.
Until you have the kind of life
that you deserve to have.
That I raised you to have.
Can you do that for me?
BECKET:
"The right kind of life."
What did she mean by that?
[CHORAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[QUACKING]
BECKET: Her final request
was to be buried
at the Redfellow Mausoleum
on the family plot
in Huntington.
PRIEST: We are
gathered here...
BECKET: When no answer came,
she arrived
at her final resting place
just off the parkway
in East Orange.
PRIEST: And Jesus tells us,
"I am the way,
"the truth, and the life.
"He who has faith..."
Or she indeed...
BECKET: In that moment,
I made up my mind.
Right then and there.
I would go straight
to the source
and demand my rightful place
at my rightful home.
[DOORBELL BUZZES]
- [MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [CAR DOOR CLOSES]
[ENGINE STARTS]
[CAR DEPARTS]
"We hope this finds you well."
After that, I enjoyed
a brief and colorful tour
of the New Jersey
foster care system.
As for Julia,
I saw her less and less...
until finally...
never at all.
And I had to wonder
if we crossed paths again,
who would I be?
A great success?
- [MUSIC STOPS]
- Or no?
- [HORNS HONKING]
- [INDISTINCT CHATTER]
BECKET: Anyway, many years
later, I found myself working
a perfectly respectable job,
the kind where you wear a suit
to the office every day.
- Morning.
- DARRYL: You're early.
Yes, sir.
Uh, why don't you jump on that
order from uptown, please?
Upper West.
[DOOR CLOSING]
[KEYS JANGLING]
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
BECKET: I still kept track
of the Redfellows
and the estate.
Sadly, their mortality rate
was irritatingly low.
And I'd pretty much accepted
that I'd never see
a penny of the fortune.
Not in this lifetime, anyway.
And maybe that was fine.
Becket?
- No fucking way! [LAUGHS]
- [EXHALES]
- Wow.
- BECKET: Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Hi! [LAUGHS]
Yeah. Wow.
[LAUGHING] Oh, my...
I can't believe it's you.
I can't believe
it's me either. How...
- Wow.
- What's with the, uh...
Are you in
the Secret Service or...
Oh.
- Yes.
- JULIA: Yeah.
BECKET: Can't really talk
about it.
So, are you living
in the city now?
Yeah, I do. I do.
A little...
- A little outside of it.
- JULIA: Oh.
Um, are you still in...
What was it?
Belleville Township.
- Right.
- BECKET: So...
You're still there?
How about you? Are you...
What, are you still
in Montclair?
Yeah. I was in London
for a while and then Dubai,
but now I'm back in
the old country. [SMACKS LIPS]
Wow. Well...
I mean, I'd...
I'd love to properly
catch up if...
you want to grab
a drink sometime?
That'd be great.
But the timing's sort of, um...
Just the timing.
Sure.
JULIA: It was great
to see you.
I'm glad you're still like this.
Like... Like what?
[SMACKS LIPS]
Just like yourself.
Oh, um...
Whatever happened to
the Redfellow family fortune?
I'll inherit it.
Someday.
Well, call me
when you've killed them all.
[DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
JULIA: Lyle,
Becket's inside there.
LYLE: Becket?
JULIA: Do you remember Becket
from school?
LYLE: [SCOFFS]
Of course he works here.
- [THUNDER RUMBLING]
- [RAIN PATTERING]
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
MARY: Promise me
that you won't quit...
until you have
the right kind of life.
[MUSIC FADES]
BECKET: There were
seven of them.
Seven Redfellows
walking the earth
while my mother
lay cold in the ground
and I lived in a duplex.
If I were to prune
a few branches
of the family tree,
where would I start?
[HIP-HOP MUSIC
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
- Taylor Exeter Redfellow.
- Thank you very much.
BECKET: Broker at his father's
financial service firm.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATION]
BECKET: My cousin wasn't
just easy to find,
he was hard to avoid
once you got anywhere
near the Financial District.
♪ Wish somebody would tell me
I'm fine ♪
♪ Losing my sight
Losing my mind ♪
♪ Wish somebody
would tell... ♪
BECKET: Even if I did it,
how would I do it?
And what then?
Would I collapse in regret?
Turn myself in?
[SCOFFS] Let's face it,
who am I kidding?
I couldn't possibly be capable
of something like that.
DARRYL: Yo, let me
grab you for a minute.
BECKET: I don't...
I don't think I understand.
We just think
you might be happier.
If I transferred to Jersey City?
It's closer to where you live.
- They have parking.
- Parking.
Are you talking about
the shipping center?
All right. Vic's kid
dropped out of school.
You're giving my job to
the owner's 19-year-old kid?
DARRYL: I'm not doing
anything, man.
This wasn't my idea.
I don't want to work
in a warehouse.
DARRYL: It's inconvenient
for me, too, okay?
- Help me out.
- BECKET: Darryl.
- DARRYL: Please?
- I'm good at this.
- I work hard, I show up.
- I know, I know.
Shouldn't that sort of thing
be rewarded?
[KNUCKLES CRACKING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[UPBEAT PARTY MUSIC PLAYING]
[HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING]
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
MAN: Bro,
this is ridiculous!
TAYLOR: Holy shit!
[ALL CHEERING]
- [BLOWS RASPBERRY]
- Come on, man.
- Are you gonna fucking do it?
- I'm fucking ready.
- Come on!
- I'm fucking ready!
- MAN: Go!
- Let's go!
- I'm doing it!
- Let's fucking go!
[CROWD CHEERING]
TAYLOR: Yeah!
[CHEERING CONTINUES]
TAYLOR: Yeah! Pick it up.
You're still poor, assholes!
- Whoa!
- TAYLOR: Whoo!
[TAYLOR SCREAMING]
Yeah!
Eat the money!
- Hey!
- [INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
BECKET: Just like before,
my cousin was easy to find.
I didn't have a plan exactly,
but the proverbial
and literal doors
were wide open.
- [FIRE BLAZING]
- [ALL CHEERING]
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
[WHOOPING]
[MUSIC FADES]
TAYLOR: World Star,
motherfucker!
BECKET: Could this be
my opportunity
to get Taylor alone?
At this point,
I could have gone home and...
maybe I would have
on a different day, but...
as the Bible says,
"The journey of a thousand miles
"begins with a single step."
- Does the Bible say that?
- No.
Oh.
[ENGINE ROARING]
[COUGHS]
[GROANS, SIGHS]
Oh, thank God.
They put fucking low ethanol
in the engine. [CHUCKLES]
[SNIFFS] Get the anchor.
Call fucking Baywatch.
Call David-fucking-Hasselhoff.
It's my boat.
- [FAINT RADIO CHATTER]
- [TAYLOR GROANS]
TAYLOR: Ah, fuck.
My helicopter. [CHUCKLES]
[COUGHS] That's my jet ski.
[SNORES]
- [ANCHOR THUDS]
- [TAYLOR COUGHS]
[CARABINER CLICKS]
[TAYLOR EXHALES]
[CHAIN RATTLING]
BECKET: Time out.
I gotta take a minute,
think this through.
Process what
I'm actually doing here,
and if I'm carrying this out...
- [TAYLOR COUGHS]
- [ANCHOR THUDS]
Wait.
Who are you?
- I'm Becket.
- [ROPE WHOOSHING]
- TAYLOR: Whoa!
- [WATER SPLASHING]
[RADIO CHATTER CONTINUES]
[WATER RIPPLING]
BECKET: By God.
Was that it?
Was it that easy?
[ENGINE ROARING]
I hate to say yes,
but it is true.
And if the whole thing
gave you a strange thrill...
Well, I guess you and I
have something in common.
Anyway...
can you believe I
attended the funeral?
- [BELL TOLLING]
- [QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
[PEOPLE MURMURING]
[PILLS RATTLING]
[DUCKS QUACKING]
Excuse me.
Are you Warren Redfellow?
Yeah, that's right.
I'm... I'm so sorry
for your loss.
Thanks.
I'm not sure I, uh...
I'm not sure I know your name.
I'm Becket.
Mary's son. I'm your nephew.
You're fucking with me.
Eighteen years old,
she had the guts to stand up
to the son of a bitch.
None of us could've done it.
Not me, at least.
I should've kept
in better touch.
Been part of her life,
part of your life.
I wish I would've gotten
a chance to know Taylor.
- He seemed like a...
- [GRUNTS]
I'm sorry.
- Don't apologize.
- It's... No.
Don't apologize. Really.
You know who did it to him?
Huh?
I assure you,
that's not the case.
WARREN: I wasn't there.
When he was coming up...
And I knew damn well that
he was going off the handle
with the cars
and the prescription.
[SLURPS]
Anyway...
what do you do, Becket?
[LIGHTS POWERING ON]
BECKET: Oh!
WARREN: Yeah,
it's been in the family
since La Guardia was in office.
I think every financial crisis
for the last 100 years
started in the boardroom.
I was here for two of 'em.
All right,
welcome to the inner sanctum.
- There, take a seat.
- BECKET: Well, this is nice.
WARREN: I got this bottle
from Dick Cheney.
- Better be good.
- [BOTTLE CLINKING]
You know, we got Taylor's spot
downstairs and...
Keep your head down, ears open.
Yeah. I'm not even
remotely qualified.
- No shit. It's nepotism.
- BECKET: I just don't...
He wasn't even
remotely qualified, either.
Neither was I at one point.
I guess the question is...
would it be right?
Becket, truth is,
I should've helped you out
a long time ago, and I didn't.
So let me do it now.
BECKET: This was
never the plan.
But I did need a job.
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
Other than that, you just
gotta save your receipts,
all right? If you don't do it,
then I can't help you.
This is your home
for the next while.
BECKET: Okay.
EMPLOYEE: Get going.
- [TELEPHONE RINGING]
- EMPLOYEE 2: Hey, man,
you already got this on email,
but here's the hard copy.
It goes up to 543,
so you should be able
- to hit 700 by close, right?
- BECKET: What?
You can't let that ring.
You gotta answer it. Answer it.
- Hello? How do you...
- [TELEPHONE RINGING]
- How do you answer it?
- EMPLOYEE 1: The blue one.
- The blue?
- EMPLOYEE 1: Yeah.
- There's no blue.
- No, it didn't devalue.
BECKET: Now, I won't bore you
with the details.
But I will say this,
the wealthiest people
in New York
don't actually make
any money whatsoever.
They keep a percentage
of what other people make,
which is a far more
adaptable way of living
and one better suited
to my overall disposition.
That's all liquid.
I'm talking about debt.
In the first week alone,
I learned the language.
Collateral, dividend,
- deduction, kicker...
- Okay, but I...
...bailing, bootstrapping,
closure, clawback,
lying, cheating,
tailing, trickery.
I finally had a real job,
and I could use the education.
[CELL PHONE VIBRATING]
I might have a fortune
of my own to manage
someday soon enough.
Someday soon enough.
Hello?
JULIA: [OVER PHONE]
Is this Becket Redfellow,
the new hire at W&R?
Apologies, who's asking?
JULIA: I hope
this isn't a bad time.
No. No.
Uh, how is married life?
[FOOTBALL GAME CHATTER ON TV]
We just got back
from our honeymoon.
Wow. Greece? Maldives?
Florida.
Oh.
Remember that time
you asked me out last year?
You were folding khaki pants,
looking sad and pathetic?
Doesn't ring a bell.
I didn't mind.
You know?
In case you felt embarrassed.
You could even
try again sometime.
See what happens.
Try... Try again?
JULIA: See what happens.
Do you wanna...
Do you wanna grab
a drink sometime?
Well, no. [CLEARS THROAT]
I'm married.
No, I... No, I... I know.
I mean, I just didn't...
But I hope we run into
each other sometime soon.
I always get so much out of it.
LYLE: Let's go! Come on!
- [FOOTBALL GAME CONTINUES]
- LYLE: Perfect!
[LINE DISCONNECTS]
BECKET: Anyway, who's next?
- [DRUMSTICKS CLACKING]
- Ooh!
- [DRUMS POUNDING]
- Be like me!
[HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING]
Hello, Internet.
I'm Noah Redfellow.
This is my domicile.
[MIMICKING GUNSHOTS, GRUNTS]
INTERVIEWER: And, like,
what would you say
are the main struggles
as an artist these days?
Probably, like,
imposter syndrome.
- INTERVIEWER: Okay.
- Not me for myself,
but, like, from other
people about me,
where they're like, "He's not...
"He's like... you're full
of shit," or whatever.
And it's like, "No, dude."
That's fuckin'
imposter syndrome.
- Do you have a day job?
- NOAH: A day job? Yeah.
Artist.
[MUSIC FADES]
[TECHNO MUSIC PLAYING]
BECKET: Now, I can't say I was
a professional at this point,
but I had a bit more confidence
than the first time around.
Enough to know
that you can, in fact,
get away with murder
and even get rewarded for it.
BECKET: Super voyeuristic,
right?
It's like the artist, you know,
is making us an accomplice.
Making us complicit.
It's just so genius.
- The artist, huh?
- Yeah.
[TECHNO MUSIC CONTINUES
OVER SPEAKERS]
I'm sorry to ask this,
you're not...
You're not Noah Redfellow,
are you?
I don't know. Am I?
Oh, I'm just...
- I'm just a huge fan.
- Wow. [CHUCKLES]
Yeah, I get a lot of that.
I... I try not to come around
too much on Fridays
'cause, you know,
people be on me.
Yeah, no, no, no.
I don't want to bother you.
- I'm sorry. Yeah.
- No, no, no. You know...
You know what I mean? Like...
You know, this next part
may sound kinda crazy.
I think you and I
actually may be cousins.
- What?
- [LAUGHING] I know.
So... so, you grew up
in Newark?
- Newark, yeah.
- Nice, dude!
That is grimy as fuck!
I mean, sure.
Yo, do you develop?
- Uh, what? Do I...
- Do you...
Do you develop,
like, your photos?
Oh, um...
No, not... not really.
No, man. You've gotta develop.
It drives me fucking crazy!
You know, no one develops,
and it's like, okay,
- if you're totally broke.
- Yeah.
Yeah, I get it.
Or if you don't have space.
Oh, fuck! Okay, um,
kick that beer.
- Kick... kick the beer?
- [CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING]
NOAH: Yeah, kick the beer.
Go ahead. Yeah!
BECKET: Like... Like that?
NOAH: Yeah, nice.
Dude, that's us.
We're all just fucking
drunk girls at a party.
We don't know what's going on.
[DOOR SLIDING OPEN]
NOAH: Huh?
This whole shit was made
by a company in Lithuania
out of, uh, recycled
toothbrushes or tampons, or...
It's, uh, medical.
[LAUGHS] You smoke?
- Uh, no.
- No?
- [LIGHTER FLICKING]
- Ooh, I'm dyin'.
Mm.
Yo, you really want to know
what we're doing up here?
[CHUCKLES] What?
[LAUGHS] I got
the old lady thinking
I quit this shit in April
but I obviously did not,
and so now I'm just in a shack
like the fucking Unabomber
just... [PUFFING] ...smoking,
you know?
- Shit.
- It's all fun and games
until they turn 30,
and then they start
asking for shit, right?
- Am I right?
- For... for sure, yeah.
NOAH: For sure.
That's what I'm saying.
WOMAN: Hello?
Mm, fuck.
Speak of the devil.
Um...
You can keep a secret, right?
We're family?
- Yeah.
- NOAH: Yeah?
Hey.
I thought you weren't
coming home till later.
Nice to see you, too, babe.
NOAH: Oh.
WOMAN: Come on, man. For real?
NOAH: What?
It was literally, like,
one or two puffs.
WOMAN: Two puffs? Really?
NOAH: That's literally
- all it was.
- WOMAN: Dude.
NOAH: Because I was...
I had to because I was showing
Beckham, this dude, right here.
Uh, I... I met him
at the show,
and he's my cousin, apparently.
- What?
- NOAH: He's my fucking cousin.
Hey. I'm Ruth.
Becket.
His name is Becket,
not Beckham. I'm sorry.
Yo, I'm so hungry
I could literally eat Sbarro.
- Can we order something?
- Yeah.
Come on. He's just gonna try
and photograph you naked.
- So don't do that.
- [MIMICKING SHUTTER CLICKING]
- RUTH: So you work in finance?
- Yeah, I... I do.
- [NOAH LAUGHS]
- RUTH: Why?
What do you mean?
I... I just mean
do you like it or...
Uh...
- Sure, I... I think so.
- RUTH: Mmm.
- Suspiciously long pause.
- BECKET: Well, it's hard work.
It's...
It's gonna pay off
at some point. I like that.
RUTH: Oh. What happens then?
BECKET: What happens
when it pays off?
- Right.
- It... it pays off.
[CHUCKLES] What?
RUTH: Right, but what happens?
What is happening?
RUTH: [CHUCKLING]
We're just...
NOAH: You're being weird
with our guest.
No, I'm just...
I'm... I'm sorry.
- I'm just curious.
- No, no, no, no, no.
NOAH: No, no,
you're being weird.
We mustn't be weird
with our guest.
We're having a conversation.
You're being a weird dude.
- Okay.
- She's from, uh, Philadelphia.
- So...
- What... What do you do?
RUTH: I, uh, I work in denim.
She saw Cardi B naked once.
- Right? Tell him.
- Okay, for the record,
I am changing careers.
I'm actually...
I'm getting my teaching
credential right now.
Teaching?
- High school lit.
- NOAH: High school is not lit.
She's gonna make me wake up
at 6:00 a.m. every morning
because of her alarm,
and then I will microwave
my own head
to kill myself
just to get some relief.
RUTH: Okay.
- [NOAH LAUGHS]
- So high school lit,
what books will you teach?
What do you...
- Dickens, Conrad.
- BECKET: Okay.
A Tale of Two Cities?
Uh, David Copperfield.
BECKET: Well, then you must
know that the...
the actual title of the book
is not David Copperfield.
RUTH: The Personal History,
Adventures, Experience,
- and Observations of David...
- BECKET: David Copperfield
the Younger
of Blunderstone Rookery...
BOTH: Which He Never Meant
to Publish on Any Account.
NOAH: Are you guys
having a virgin-off?
- What the fuck is this?
- [CHUCKLES]
[LAUGHS]
"I'm David Copperfield.
"I'm just a nerd. I'm a nerd.
I... [BABBLES]
"Cut off my dick.
I don't use it anymore."
Guys, I gotta go.
I just realized
I hate both of you. [LAUGHS]
Well, it was nice to meet ya.
BECKET: You as well.
Do you wanna come back
for dinner on Thursday?
We're having a...
- a group thing.
- Sure.
- Cool.
- Okay.
- RUTH: Uh, bye.
- Uh...
- I'll... I'll text you. Yeah.
- All right.
- All right, all right.
- [FUNK MUSIC PLAYING]
WARREN: Adjustable markets,
right? Let's see...
BECKET: This was a new
situation altogether.
Because let's face it,
the first time,
I'd gotten lucky.
This time, I would need a plan.
A real plan.
People are gonna figure it out.
- BECKET: But what?
- It's a goddamn,
- you know, time bomb.
- WOMAN: Yeah, it is.
San Francisco is the worst city
in the United States.
WOMAN: Why?
MAN: It's pretentious.
WOMAN: There
is no there there.
MAN: It's gentrified.
There's too many
art school drop-outs.
I think it's a great place.
If... if you have kids,
you have the ocean.
You've got the mountains.
Do you want kids?
I don't know. Maybe.
Cool. I get it.
What about you?
- Kids? Oh.
- Yeah.
I mean,
I don't hate kids, but...
Wait. I hate kids.
- [LAUGHS] I hate kids.
- Yeah.
NOAH: I hate 'em.
Uh, I mean, you know, not,
like, Eastern European kids.
- Like, like, like...
- WOMAN: Oh, my God. What?
Well, they're very quiet
because they're traumatized
and they work very hard,
I think.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
- [WOMAN LAUGHS]
- MAN: What? [LAUGHS]
RUTH: Who told you this?
NOAH: Frankles.
How? What do you mean,
like, sun exposure?
[SOFT INTRIGUING
MUSIC PLAYING]
BECKET: The whole thing
was simple enough in theory.
Add sulphur
and potassium chloride
to photographic stop bath
and you've essentially
made dynamite.
They'd think poor Noah
made a bad choice
- in cleaning supplies.
- [HISSING]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATION]
Such as the bottle they'd find
under the kitchen sink
right behind the vinegar.
The final ingredient
would be a single spark
and no one would ever question
where that came from.
Um, where's, um...
- What's his name?
- Yeah. Uh, I'll check.
- I'll check.
- Oh, no, no. Let me check.
- I love that guy.
- Okay.
What...
What is his name, though?
- Becket. Yeah.
- Becket?
Yo, Bagel? You fall in?
[GLASS SHATTERS]
[DOOR OPENING]
- [NOAH HUMMING]
- [DOOR CLOSES]
[NOAH SCATTING]
- [CLANGS]
- Whoa.
You caught me.
Caught you doing what?
I'm sorry.
I couldn't help myself.
- NOAH: Hey, well...
- I know.
[CHUCKLES]
You just had to have it.
I had to have it.
It's too good.
Well...
- [MARKER SCRIBBLING]
- "To Bagel...
"Love White Basquiat."
RUTH: Okay. Okay, sounds good.
- Get home safe.
- WOMAN: Bye, guys.
RUTH: Bye, you guys.
Drink water.
WOMAN: Thank you.
Thank you so much.
RUTH: Thank you for coming.
MAN: See ya later.
WOMAN: Thanks for having us.
- RUTH: Great seeing you.
- Good to see you.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
If I didn't know any better...
[CHUCKLES]
I'd say you're trying
to get me alone.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
- BECKET: Mm.
- [EXHALES]
That's a little outrageous,
by the way.
The timing.
I mean, we fall for each other,
the boyfriend ends up dead.
Might as well call
the sheriff myself, but...
The clock was set.
And it was about
eight minutes later when...
[ZAPS]
[EXPLOSION]
[CAR ALARMS BLARING]
[SIRENS BLARING]
Do you have any sympathy lilies?
[BELL TOLLS]
BECKET: I wanted nothing more
than to pick up
where we left off, but...
I had to give her time.
Making a move too quickly
would be pretty ungentlemanly,
given the situation.
And surely, she needed
some time to recover and...
WOMAN: Excuse me.
BECKET: Ah, shit.
- WOMAN: Hi.
- Hi.
- Is it Becket?
- Yes.
I'm Agent Pinfield.
I'm with the FBI.
This is my partner,
Agent Matthews.
- Hi.
- How you doing?
Great.
So you are an heir
to the estate,
is that correct?
The...
The Redfellow estate?
No. Uh, not to my knowledge.
Not that you're aware of?
Well, my mom, she, um...
I guess she grew up a Redfellow.
They had a falling out. Um...
But you came to the funeral.
Well, I'm a friend of Noah.
Uh, I... I was.
God, I, uh, yeah,
I was friends with Noah.
So you're not set
to inherit anything?
Look, I... I work a 9 to 5
like you guys. If I...
I mean,
if I were set to inherit,
what, $10 billion,
I think I'd change my hours.
MATTHEWS: [CHUCKLES] Me too.
Sorry, do you mind
if I ask what...
what this is all about?
Sure. When, um,
two family members
die like this in a row,
the bureau
has certain protocols.
Okay.
- [CHAMPAGNE BOTTLE POPS]
- [ALL CHEERING, LAUGHING]
WARREN: You all know
what they say,
you gotta be the meanest
son of a bitch on the block?
Well, here I am talking
about a kid
who got himself off the floor
by being a decent human being.
Started at the mail desk
10 months ago.
I think some of you
gave him shit, by the way.
Lucky I'm not naming
names, Johan.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Seriously, we all like it
when a good guy
makes a little progress.
Anyway, my man,
he's got a client already,
so let's get back to work, huh?
You can
take your drinks with you.
I won't tell the boss,
I promise.
- [SIGHS]
- [DOOR OPENS]
JULIA: Tell me something.
Does he really think
you got here by hard work?
You're his nephew,
for Christ's sake.
I'd invite you to stay,
but I have a client.
I am your client.
I need a loan.
You know my husband inherited
his father's brokerage,
but he didn't inherit
his father's talent
for running a brokerage.
I didn't know how bad
the bleeding had gotten
because he never told me,
so now I'm here...
and...
I'm not telling him.
You know
this isn't a bank, right?
Well, this would be
a special case, wouldn't it?
- How much do you need?
- JULIA: Not a fortune.
But enough.
Well, I have relationships.
I can go through
the proper channels.
- JULIA: God.
- We'd have to do
a background check.
Sounds so official.
What did you have in mind?
I don't know.
Maybe something under the table.
Julia...
Mmm-hmm?
Um, I just...
JULIA: Love the office,
by the way.
Those are my keys.
Look...
We should talk again,
and I wouldn't wait too long.
The opportunity might grow
legs and walk out the door.
Just one more thing, though.
Have you heard
about the Redfellows?
What about 'em?
Taylor? Noah?
I wonder who's next.
If I were you,
I might be nervous.
I'll expect to hear from you.
Until then,
I'm sure you'll make a killing.
[INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING]
BECKET: It was
probably nothing.
Either way,
my style of murder so far
had very little style at all.
I needed to be more careful.
- Hey, Ethan.
- ETHAN: Yes, sir.
Weird question.
Are you, like, a 40 regular?
Am I what?
[ALL CHEERING]
[BAND PLAYING UPLIFTING MUSIC]
Yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes!
Oh, my God!
BECKET: The next Redfellow
in line was a true outlier.
I mean, they were all
extreme personalities
but only one had managed
to build something like this.
Whatever this was.
[GUITAR SOLO PLAYING]
Does He interfere
with your will?
- CHURCHGOERS: No!
- No. Uh-uh.
Does capital "H," He,
do all the work for you?
ALL: No!
You gotta will your own, right?
Guess why.
That's the way He made you.
BECKET: Now two
was a coincidence.
Three, that would be a pattern.
PASTOR: That's yours.
BECKET: But Steven Redfellow
had no shortage of enemies.
The man had been indicted
in two different countries
for money laundering,
and let's not forget the lawsuit
with his former
business manager.
The crossroads, yet again.
BECKET: So if Steven ended up
in a dumpster somewhere...
perhaps it would be God's will.
[CHRISTIAN ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
STEVEN: ...dicking us around.
Yeah.
Look, nobody doesn't
call you for three days
and thinks you're
a priority, okay?
No. No, they're
pulling our leg, man.
[MOUTHING "ONE MINUTE"]
Oh. Mmm-hmm.
Yeah, that's 'cause
they're in real estate, Jason.
All right, look.
Uh, I gotta bounce.
I will hit you back later,
all right?
All right, peace.
Whoo! I just get so fricken
hyped on first Sundays, right?
- Oh, come on.
- Oh.
Ben Johnson,
Midwest Christian Magazine.
Oh, come on.
I know who you are. Please.
Have a seat.
Look, I'm sorry we couldn't
sit down last month.
I was actually in Korea.
We're opening a church over
there, so it's exciting stuff.
- Korea?
- It's a magical place.
Magical people.
Complicated tax laws, so...
[CHUCKLES]
I think our readers
just want to know
the man behind the movement.
Let's do it!
Let's do it.
Uh, you want to start
with the photos?
- Sure. Yeah.
- Um...
Can you tell me about
this one right here?
Okay. Uh, that's me
and the President of Armenia.
President of Panama. Look,
the church has been lucky
to make some good friends
over the years.
That is me with El Chapo.
Super interesting dude
if you actually,
I don't know, talk to him.
I mean... [CHUCKLES]
But the press barbequed me
for that one too.
I'm not sure
if you know this, but...
I'm from like a, kind of
a well-known family.
I don't know. It just means
people are always
trying to knock me down.
You know, take me out the game.
I just always tell myself
it's nothing my buddy J.C.
didn't have to deal with, right?
It's, like, don't hate on me
just 'cause my dad's a big deal,
or whatever, right?
Amen.
STEVEN: Yeah, you get it.
You know who else got it?
Mayor of Kyoto.
God put it on my heart
to open a church there, too.
And he gave me this. Oh.
[CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
Look at that.
[STEVEN MIMICS SWORD SWISHING]
Whoa, whoa, whoa. [CHUCKLES]
- Ooh-ah!
- [CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
Here, feel it. Feel the tip.
Feel how sharp that is.
Feel it. Come on.
You gotta feel it.
Okay. [CLEARS THROAT]
That's it, just touch it.
- Wow. Ow. [CHUCKLES]
- STEVEN: Right? [LAUGHS]
STEVEN: Yeah, it's, like,
razor sharp, right?
So sharp.
I can give you a shave
from all the way
over here, right?
Well, I shaved
this morning, so...
I know it was you.
I knew it was you
before you walked in the door.
See, Ben Johnson retired
eight months ago, so...
Your other victims
might've been too dumb
to put it together, but not me.
You don't get out of here
until you come clean.
Come clean? What?
STEVEN: Come on.
Come on, let me hear it.
BECKET: Hear what?
What... what do you want?
The truth. Come on.
You gotta
let that shit out. Right?
Look, I think you have me
confused with someone else.
- I know everything! Say it!
- [YELPS]
[HESITATES]
What do you want me to say?
- What do you want me to say?
- Give it to me!
- Come on! Come on!
- Hey! Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Get it out there in the air.
Exorcise that shit!
Okay, okay, okay.
I lied. I lied. I lied.
- I'm not Ben Johnson. Okay.
- STEVEN: You're not, are you?
- Who are you?
- I'm Becket. I'm Becket.
I'm... I'm your cousin!
[UPBEAT MUSIC
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
[MUSIC STOPS]
What'd you just say?
I'm your...
I'm... I'm your cousin.
You're not from The Post?
You're not writing a hit piece?
You're not that guy?
What?
Oh.
[LAUGHS AWKWARDLY] Okay.
Uh, this is embarrassing.
[CHUCKLES]
I just get so paranoid
with this job, you know?
It's... Whew!
Whew!
Oh, man. I shoulda known
we were family.
It's like looking
in a freakin' mirror.
[SLURPING]
[EXHALES] Something's
a little off with that.
BECKET: Did you know
that tropane alkaloids
are an active ingredient
in most pre-workout supplements?
If you have
too much of the stuff,
you might have
a massive heart attack.
[BELL TOLLS]
BECKET: And by too much,
I mean about 1,500 milligrams.
And the last thing the church
wanted was an investigation.
I'm sure
you know all about that.
Anyway...
[POIGNANT PIANO MUSIC PLAYING]
Finally,
I was getting somewhere.
Wasn't I?
MARY: Promise me
that you won't quit.
Not until you have
the right kind of life.
[POIGNANT PIANO MUSIC
CONTINUES]
[LAUGHS]
RUTH: Can you keep a secret?
BECKET: Surprisingly well,
actually.
I was gonna break up with him
that weekend.
And now he's gone, and I know
I'm supposed to feel,
like, devastated
but I... I don't...
I don't. [SIGHS]
No. You feel what
you're supposed to feel.
Does that make me
a terrible person?
No.
I think it makes you honest.
I don't know. I think
I'm still going to hell.
- [CHUCKLES]
- Man, you're talking to a guy
who works on Wall Street.
RUTH: Oh, you're
definitely going to hell.
Do you want to grab dinner
this week?
Yes. [LAUGHS]
Um, my office can grab us
a reservation at The Modern.
Uh, it's midtown. Um...
I've never been there,
but I hear it's great.
Yeah.
Or we could keep it simple
and cook something?
Yeah, simple. I love simple.
[MUSIC STOPS]
[BECKET EXHALES]
I know. Dramatic, right?
What are you doing?
JULIA: What are you doing?
We had an agreement.
First off, how did you
get in my apartment?
I took a key
right in front of you.
No, I remember.
Two calls, two emails,
nothing back?
- I've been occupied.
- JULIA: With what?
Occupations.
Go on.
Come on.
How long have
we known each other?
- Quite some time.
- JULIA: So you should
be able to tell me anything.
I'll go first.
We're flat broke.
My husband lied to me for years,
and he's an absolute coward.
Now you go.
I have nothing to tell you.
I would never judge.
BECKET: For what?
Well, that would sour things
between us, wouldn't it?
I don't like it sour.
I like it sweet.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
Oh, my God. Julia. I'm s...
[CLEARS THROAT]
- JULIA: What?
- You have to go.
JULIA: Are you
fucking kidding me?
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- JULIA: What the hell?
I'm sorry.
You've gotta go.
- Hey.
- Hi.
It's a bit of a culinary
disaster in there.
Oh. Uh, oh, no. [LAUGHS]
Everything okay or...?
Uh, do you want
to go out to eat?
Yeah, sure.
Great.
[RUTH LAUGHS]
These students,
I love them, but...
Tell me about it.
RUTH: They all want
to be millionaires,
but none of them
want an actual job.
BECKET: They all gotta
have a dream, right?
- I get it, but...
- Thank you.
Thank you.
I mean, I think it's...
I think it's good to want more.
Okay, gun to your head.
What would you even do
with a billion dollars?
Why do you have
a gun to my head?
Answer the question.
Get those chopstick guns
out of my face.
[LAUGHS] Answer the question.
- I don't know.
- [RUTH CHUCKLES]
I'd take you
to a better restaurant.
Working in fashion
was my lifelong goal, right?
Like, I had tunnel vision.
And now all I can think about
is the time I put in.
What, uh, we shouldn't
chase what we want?
The thing is,
I think I knew the whole time.
- Knew what?
- That I didn't like it.
That I might be happier
making shit money
and having a cactus garden.
It's just scary to dream small.
Nobody teaches us
how to do that.
FATHER MORRIS: Uh, sorry, I...
I don't mean
to interrupt, but...
at this point, you met someone,
you had a good career.
Was that not enough?
Enough what?
Look...
It wasn't lost on me.
I had a good job,
a budding romance.
Maybe I should hit pause
on the systematic killing
of my entire family.
Reservation at Manilla's,
Friday?
Friday? Get outta here.
- [VOICEMAIL BEEPS]
- No way.
JULIA: Becket, it's me again.
And you're not answering...
again.
I wouldn't ignore me
much longer.
Something bad might happen,
muchacho.
BECKET: But how
could I quit now?
I mean, not even one had been
investigated as a murder.
Was I that good?
Maybe I was that good.
Of course, by this point,
the family had realized
that something was up.
- [CHILDREN LAUGHING]
- INTERVIEWER: CEO.
And now, adoption icon.
BECKET:
Take my Aunt Cassandra.
She had gotten sort of famous
for adopting, like, 11 kids
from 11 different countries
and they spoke 11 different
languages around the house.
[CHILDREN CLAMORING]
Okay, I am on the phone.
We can see that, right?
Do we know phone,
or do I need to tattoo it
on my fucking forehead?
BECKET: She heard about
the deaths in the family
and got a laser-based security
system installed
in all four of her houses.
But there wasn't
a security system
at the Blessings
of the Desert Day Spa
where she spent
every Tuesday afternoon.
I'm sorry to disturb you.
We're offering complimentary
teeth whitening services
until 5 o'clock,
if you're interested.
I have some literature
on the process,
safety information,
if you'd like.
CASSANDRA: I didn't
come here to read.
Blessings.
The special ingredient
was carbamide peroxide
which is so close
to the acidic agent
found in teeth whitener
that the police thought
she must have bought
an off-brand batch
during her last adoption trip
to Cambodia.
[CASSANDRA SPEAKING, MUFFLED]
It's tingling.
- [BELL TOLLS]
- [DUCKS QUACKING]
[CELL PHONE VIBRATES]
BECKET: Then there's
my Uncle McArthur.
Sir, you've got about
a 30-knot wind
coming out
of the north-northwest.
- Just so you know.
- Thanks, but I think
I can handle
some goddamn wind, chief.
BECKET: This guy owned, like,
half The National Air
and Space Museum.
And while the rest of us
were planning
a long weekend at Key West,
he was planning an actual
trip to the actual moon.
JOURNALIST: McArthur,
what do you say to the critics
who see you spending
$50 million to fly to space
when half your employees
don't have health insurance?
Fifty? More like ninety.
Look, if I could do this kind
of thing for cheap, I would.
But it's incredibly expensive.
- Gassed up?
- ASSISTANT: Yes, sir.
MCARTHUR: Spot check?
ASSISTANT: Yes, sir.
MCARTHUR: Where's my coffee,
by the way?
BECKET: Here you go.
Lock and load.
BECKET: All it took
was a laminated pass
and a shirt from the mall.
[ALARM BLARING]
MAN: [OVER RADIO] Charlie 17,
you are very low, over.
[BELL TOLLS]
1,500 square feet,
three bedrooms, doorman.
You ever have a doorman before?
- I barely had a door.
- [REALTOR CHUCKLES]
REALTOR: It changes your life.
I'm not even joking around.
This is original marble
from, uh, Italy.
And if you look out there,
that's what you pay
the money for.
So would you want to live here?
[VEHICLE HONKS]
With me?
I know
it's a little fast, but...
I'd really
like to have you here.
I'd love it, actually.
If I'm being honest.
Uh... [CHUCKLES]
Um...
Yeah.
I'd love that too.
Now, I know the place is a lot
but Warren's gonna give me
a bridge loan
and the neighborhood's
appreciating...
RUTH: Hey, hey.
I liked you when you lived
in Newark and took the bus.
You know that, right?
What?
Nothing.
By the way, I can fire you
at any time, but I won't.
- [ALL LAUGHING]
- [STAMMERS, CHUCKLES]
To continue with this story,
and he said, he's, like...
"What are you talking about?
Where are you?"
And I was, like,
"I'm in Highland Park."
He was, like, "No..."
BECKET: As for the next
Redfellow in line,
you can probably
guess who it was.
[WARREN LAUGHS]
BECKET: But by now,
I couldn't imagine lifting
a finger against my uncle,
much less doing the man harm.
And by that point, things were
going decently well.
The job, living situation...
FATHER MORRIS:
You were content.
Without the wealth.
Without the inheritance.
Well...
Maybe you're right.
Maybe I was...
content.
Content enough.
And I suppose I had
more important things
to think about.
RUTH: My mom's gonna
want Zinfandel.
I think we're making
the right choice, by the way.
Having an engagement party
at your home just feels,
better than
at a bar or something.
I totally agree.
RUTH: I'm still thinking
about your family.
All the crazy shit.
Okay.
I don't mean to obsess,
but don't you think that it's...
BECKET: I'm not even
a part of that family.
Whatever's going on, it's got
nothing to do with us.
Besides, it's probably
over anyway.
RUTH: What makes you say that?
I don't know.
Just sayin' it.
- [TRAFFIC BUSTLING]
- [DISTANT SIRENS BLARING]
PINFIELD: Excuse me.
Mr. Redfellow?
Becket Redfellow?
How you doing today?
[BECKET CLEARS THROAT]
MATTHEWS: Nice office
you got here.
I like it. [CHUCKLES]
PINFIELD:
Just so we understand,
you said you're not an heir
to the estate, is that correct?
As far as I know.
Well, we did
a little research, and...
Congratulations.
BECKET: Wow.
Uh, it's just a little...
I... I had no idea.
Hmm. Can you answer
a few questions for us?
Yeah, I'm... I'm sorry.
Um, I... I really had no idea.
This is...
PINFIELD: Nobody's
arguing with you.
MATTHEWS: Can you tell us
where you were
on the afternoon of April 10th?
It would've been a Sunday.
BECKET: Oh...
April 10th. Okay. Here we go.
MATTHEWS: You're
fucking kidding me.
He remembers when
and where he bought a hot dog.
Is that even him?
I don't know.
Can you see who it is?
PINFIELD: I can't see shit.
MATTHEWS: Me neither.
PINFIELD: All right,
follow him.
WOMAN: Rothburn's going down,
and Bellman's gonna go too.
They're minutes away,
I guarantee it.
MAN: I say we dump
whatever we can cut loose
before the markets catch wind.
WOMAN: We can say we were
forced into it, which is true.
No.
I spent 35 years
earning the trust
of these shareholders.
I'm not throwing them
to the sharks
in one afternoon.
[CELLPHONE RINGING]
- Oh, shit.
- BECKET: What?
[WARREN EXHALES DEEPLY]
- Goddamn! [GRUNTING]
- Oh, whoa. Oh, oh, oh!
- [GASPING]
- MAN: Is he all right?
- Becket...
- Call an ambulance!
WARREN: Pass me that water,
will ya?
[GRUNTS, GULPING]
[EXHALES, SIGHS]
[CHUCKLES]
Listen, I'm not
gonna mince words.
You want to chase that rabbit
down the hole, huh?
Okay. That money rabbit.
Everybody loves a good chase.
And you're good at it.
But here I am,
61 years old and...
you're the only visitor
I've had all day.
Go find that person
in your life, Becket.
Whoever it is.
Work at loving them.
I mean, really work.
'Cause...
at the end of the day...
it's the only job that pays.
[DUCKS QUACKING]
[CHORAL MUSIC PLAYING]
BECKET: It was in this
unhappy moment
that I realized an ironic truth.
There is only one left.
MAN: You can either
get rid of it,
or do what you like.
But not here.
Not under this roof.
And I think you know
I have to stand by that.
A man of my word.
BECKET: One left.
But what use was it
to fantasize?
I had put all that behind me.
Hey, Becket. Letter for you.
- Thanks, Brian.
- Yep.
[CHORAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [MUSIC STOPS]
- [CELL PHONE VIBRATING]
- Hey.
- He invited me.
RUTH: [OVER PHONE] What?
My grandfather.
To a dinner party
at the estate. [CHUCKLES]
- Hello?
- Uh, I just...
I... I thought you said
you would never do that?
- Never do what?
- RUTH: Never meet the guy.
Wait, when is this?
- Tonight.
- It's Friday.
- BECKET: I know.
- Friday.
BECKET: Oh, shit.
Ruth, I may not have
this opportunity again.
He never sees anyone.
RUTH: You may not have
this opportunity again?
- I don't know.
- Yeah, you're right.
So be home by 7:00
or you will miss
your own fucking engagement
party, like... [SCOFFS]
Right. Of course. Of course.
Okay.
I love you, by the way.
I'm gonna call you back.
Package for Mr. Redfellow.
Remember to breathe.
Very important.
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
Taylor drowned.
He went to Princeton
on a swimming scholarship
and he drowned.
I became more than a bit
suspicious right then.
So I had a little friend
follow you.
Aren't those great?
I'm really happy
I went with black and white.
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
[GRUNTS, SLAMS TABLE]
BECKET: What do you want?
Finish it.
I'm under investigation
by the FBI.
And yet here you are.
It's almost as if, I don't know,
they don't quite have a case.
Which is bananas.
Anyway, I will need
a down payment.
- A what?
- 300,000 by five o'clock.
Shit.
JULIA: I'm done
fucking around.
It's...
You gotta be shitting me.
You still have a company
checkbook, right?
You still have access
to the accounts?
Deliver the cheques
to my husband.
He's in his office in Hoboken,
waiting on you like
a patient little puppy.
You have 30 minutes.
Any longer than that
and she'll get a package
just like the one I gave you.
Who will get a package?
Your little girlfriend,
who do you think?
Cardozo High School
in Bayside, Queens, right?
She's in for quite the shock.
For what it's worth,
I was hoping
for a different arrangement.
Something a bit more fun.
But you blew it, Becket.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Brian.
Call Fritzer in Vienna.
We're gonna sell P&G.
Tell him to name his price.
Call? Am I allowed to do that?
What? Just do it.
MATTHEWS: Uh-huh.
I've got him right now.
Yes, ma'am.
Headed North on Hanover.
That's North, Hanover.
Sir?
Excuse me, sir!
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
RECEPTIONIST: Excuse me?
He's just not here.
- I don't...
- [DOOR OPENS]
Is that her?
Gimme that.
I'm here. I got your cheques,
you sociopathic,
conniving bitch.
Jesus Christ, Becket.
This could've been anyone.
Call it off.
Well, just write
the checks first, will you?
- I want to be positive...
- [RECEIVER CLATTERING]
Cheer up, Lyle.
You're about to make
a lot of money.
LYLE: I'm not gonna make
any money. Are you kidding?
She's just gonna take it
and leave.
I'm not the one
she wants anyway.
But you... you're really
coming up in the world, huh?
Just... Just a little bastard.
Just a little bastard
from Newark. [CHUCKLES]
[SLAPS]
[LYLE GROANS SOFTLY]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[SOBBING]
BECKET: I'd already committed
embezzlement and assault.
So fuck it.
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
AUTOMATED VOICE: Going down.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[RAIN PATTERING]
[SIGHS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[KEYPAD CLICKING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Hi!
How are you?
Thank you for coming.
[RAIN PATTERING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GRUNTS]
[DOOR SLAMS]
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
- [THUNDER RUMBLING]
- [FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
On account of the storm,
I decided to cancel
the festivities tonight.
But I just couldn't
turn you down.
Whitelaw.
[CLEARS THROAT] Becket.
Did you bring an appetite?
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
So...
Been working your way
up the financial ladder.
Is that right?
Trying to.
I understand
you've come a long ways.
Must've really put in the hours.
A filthy business, though,
isn't it?
How do you mean?
Come on.
One professional to another,
you must have, uh...
broken a few heads,
bumped off some of
the competition, no?
Two or three, maybe.
Would you take any of it back?
Because this sort of life is...
it isn't cut out for everyone,
is it?
It would make some people tired.
Old.
Lonely.
Regretful.
But me, I've always felt
I know a certain truth,
that the only thing
that really hurts us in life
is the voice
of our own conscience...
telling us a story
about right and wrong.
And if you know
how to turn your head
just right into the wind,
you can make that voice
go down to a whisper.
After a while...
you might never hear it at all.
[CLOCK CHIMING]
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
She was my favorite, by the way.
Sharpest of the bunch.
Always knew what she wanted
and willing to fight for it.
Why didn't you help her...
when she needed it?
You know where
this is all going, don't you?
Come on.
I wanna show you something...
before Charles
brings out the pudding.
[DOOR OPENS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
A trench gun,
belonged to your
great-great-uncle,
World War I.
These... These things
mortified the Germans.
They'd never seen anything
like it.
- [GUN COCKING]
- [SHELL CLATTERING]
Here.
Go ahead.
Draw a bead on something.
I want you to try this.
Here.
Right here.
[EXHALES SOFTLY]
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
[MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
I better be going.
Where to?
Home.
You're almost there.
[GUN CLICKING]
WHITELAW: [SIGHING] Well...
you better go quickly then.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[DOORKNOB RATTLING]
[BECKET SIGHS]
[RATTLING]
[METAL CREAKING IN DISTANCE]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[LOCKS CLICKING]
[DOOR OPENS]
[SHUDDERS]
- [GUNSHOT]
- [BECKET YELPS]
- [GRUNTS]
- [DOOR CLOSES]
[WHITELAW GROANING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[BOTH GROANING]
- [SQUELCHING]
- [GRUNTS]
Go on and fuckin' run!
Doors are boarded up
from the outside.
- Charles made sure of that.
- Shit!
- [GLASS SHATTERING]
- [ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
- [BECKET PANTING]
- WHITELAW: There's no way out!
Go on. Tire yourself!
Come to my house to kill me?
- [ELECTRICITY BUZZING]
- [GLASS SHATTERING]
You best have done that
when I gave you the chance.
[GRUNTS, PANTS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Okay. Okay.
[PANTING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
- [SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
- [BREATHING HEAVILY]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[PANTING]
[BOW SNAPS, CLATTERS]
- [GUNSHOT]
- [OBJECTS CLATTERING]
[GUNSHOT]
[GUN CLICKS]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [GUN COCKING]
- [MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
[GROANS]
- [BLOOD GUSHING]
- [CHOKING]
[EXHALES]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
BECKET: Believe this.
My final murder
was not a murder at all
but a perfectly legitimate
act of self-defense.
OFFICER: All right.
Sheriff's Department's
on the way.
BECKET: Okay.
OFFICER: They're just gonna
talk to you, okay?
All right. All right. Um...
[CLEARS THROAT]
I... I need to... I need to go
'cause I have
my engagement party.
It started an hour ago.
OFFICER:
Whose engagement party?
BECKET: It's mine.
DETECTIVE: So you had
no relationship
with your grandfather?
I'd never met him
before tonight.
- Not even once?
- BECKET: Never.
Look, if I'm not
legally required to be here,
I need to leave.
You're not legally required to,
but, uh...
I'd prefer if you stay.
Okay.
[CAR ALARM CHIRPING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
- [SIGHS]
- [DOOR OPENS]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[BECKET SIGHS SOFTLY]
[SIGHING]
[EXHALES]
I'll give you
the full explanation.
You're withholding
something from me.
You've been withholding
[SIGHS]
So right now...
you have to tell me what's up...
or I'm out.
[EXHALES]
[SIGHS]
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
BECKET: Sometimes in life,
you gotta take a deep breath,
come clean
to the person you love.
This was not one of those times.
I only told her
what she'd see on the news.
NEWS REPORTER: ... is indeed
dead, and it seems...
BECKET:
My grandfather was gone.
NEWS REPORTER:
...some sort of altercation...
BECKET:
And as for the fortune,
well...
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIGHS]
- [ALL APPLAUDING]
- [CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING]
BECKET: The right kind
of life.
This had to be it, right?
Sure, she had a few misgivings,
but we can handle that later.
For now, I was rich.
And being rich
is even better than you imagine.
[MUSIC CONCLUDES]
[CLOCK TICKING]
You know I mentioned earlier,
this is a tragedy.
Still is.
Donald Macnamara, my wife.
- Such a pleasure.
- Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
- RUTH: Hi.
- Nancy Dillard, the Dillards.
- Nice to meet you.
- NANCY: Mmm-hmm.
Megan Pinfield.
FBI.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Hello.
Can you shut that door
behind you, please?
[BECKET SIGHS]
Look, not to be uncouth,
but this is...
heroically bad timing.
Yeah, you're under arrest.
I need you to stay calm
and cooperate.
- I'm under arrest? For what?
- For murder.
Of who?
Lyle Archdale.
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING]
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
RUTH: Hey, wait!
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
RUTH: What do we do?
What do we do?
[ENGINE ROARING]
Ruth, I love...
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
BECKET: Can you believe it?
After all this,
I'd go down for a killing
I didn't even commit.
NEWS REPORTER: Now we wanna
point out to listeners
that Becket Redfellow
crossed state lines,
which is why his trial
is unfolding in federal court
where murder can still mean
capital punishment
for citizens of New Jersey.
As we can see
from these security tapes,
Mr. Redfellow
burst into the office
at approximately 5:03 p.m.,
and then emerged
just four minutes later,
which is consistent
with the estimated time
of Mr. Archdale's death.
Now, we've heard
from the coroner
that he estimates
the time of death
between 5:06 and 5:15 p.m.
And we've heard
from the eyewitness
in the hallway,
who positively identifies
Mr. Redfellow.
Sir, can you confirm that
this is the murder weapon?
Uh, I can confirm
that it is, yes.
And did you find
the defendant's fingerprints
on the murder weapon?
FORENSICS EXPERT:
I did, yes.
How certain are you that, uh,
these are his fingerprints?
FORENSICS EXPERT:
I'm 100% certain.
BECKET: A letter opener.
My entire life
because of a letter opener.
PROSECUTOR: You were the first
to find your husband's body.
Is that correct?
Yes.
Tell me. Were you in love with
Mr. Redfellow at the time?
[JULIA SNIFFLES]
Yes. [CRYING]
PROSECUTOR:
And he with you?
Becket Redfellow
has been in love with me
his entire life. [SNIFFLES]
[JULIA SOBBING]
I just never thought he would
do something like this.
[SOBBING]
I'm sorry.
JUDGE: Will the defense
please rise?
Upon the verdict,
the jury finds the defendant,
Becket Redfellow,
guilty of murder
in the first degree
as charged in the indictment
and that the punishment of death
- shall be imposed.
- [INDISTINCT CONVERSATION]
JUDGE: May the sentence
be recorded by the clerk.
May God rest his soul.
Thank you.
[GAVEL BANGS]
BECKET: I wish I could find
the right words
to describe this juncture
in my story.
[DOOR BUZZING]
[DOOR SLAMS]
PRISON GUARD: Cell 15, secure!
BECKET: But there are
no right words.
[EXHALES]
There's only time.
- And silence.
- [CLOCK TICKING]
[CLOCK TICKING]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[FOOTSTEPS HALT]
- PRISON GUARD: Yo.
- [THUMPING ON RAILS]
You got a visitor.
PRISON GUARD:
You got three minutes.
[BECKET SIGHS]
[INHALES]
You must be quite the catch
back there.
You got a big day
coming up, huh?
You remember that game
we used to play as kids?
I'd have a secret, and...
you'd try to guess what it was.
If you've got
something to say, say it.
All right.
I'll give you a hint.
- It involves handwriting.
- You're foul.
You're a lump of coal
with makeup.
I'd rather die in here
than be with you.
I'll give you another hint.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Lyle...
when I found him like that...
I found something else, too.
And beautifully written,
I might add.
What's with the white?
Are you boys playing doctor
back there?
Did Lyle leave a note?
Is that what you're saying?
- JULIA: You know...
- If Lyle wrote a note...
- I think I might just leave...
- If that's what you're saying,
in the name of all things holy,
you have to release it.
- Oh, now you want to talk?
- What do you want?
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
- Becket...
What could you possibly have
to offer?
No, no, no, no, no!
Hey, hey, hey! Stop!
- That's it! [GRUNTING]
- Tell me! Stop! Stop!
I have 30 seconds!
- PRISON GUARD: You got 25.
- Okay.
- Sit down.
- Julia!
Julia, come here, please!
Please!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Okay.
What do you want?
- Just give me a moment.
- [SLAMS FIST]
I'm gonna die in 24 hours.
You don't want that to happen.
I know you don't want that
to happen.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Give me everything.
- Sign it over to...
- [LINE DISCONNECTS]
[ALARM BUZZING]
[THUDS]
[EXHALES]
PRISON GUARD:
You need anything else?
Got a priest?
Well, that was some hours ago.
And if you're curious
why I've been so calm
and self-assured
for a man
set to be executed in...
it's because I thought
our friend Julia, might, uh...
might come through in the end.
[INHALES]
I wonder if she's coming.
FATHER MORRIS:
"The Lord is my shepherd
"I shall not want.
"He maketh me to lie down
in green pastures.
"He leadeth me
beside the still waters."
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
"He restoreth my soul.
"He leadeth me
in the paths of righteousness
"for his name's sake.
"Yea, though I walk through
"the valley
of the shadow of death
"I will fear no evil
"for thou art with me.
"Thy rod and thy staff
they comfort me."
[CLOCK TICKING]
[FATHER MORRIS CONTINUES
INDISTINCTLY]
PRISON GUARD: Redfellow.
You're not gonna
fuckin' believe this.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
POLICE CHIEF:
First and foremost,
we have absolute faith
in our forensic team...
[CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY]
PRISON GUARD: Open 15.
[DOOR SLIDING OPEN]
Let's go.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[RUSTLING]
[DOOR BUZZING]
[SIGHS SOFTLY]
[SIGHS]
BECKET: You came.
[CAR DOOR CLOSES,
ENGINE STARTS]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[ENGINE ACCELERATING]
[SIGHS HEAVILY]
[LATIN POP MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIGHS]
All right.
[MUSIC CONTINUES PLAYING]
FEMALE CHORUS:
♪ Hey, hey, dee-dee ♪
♪ Take me back to Piauí ♪
BECKET: I told you
this is a tragedy.
It's not about me, is it?
I think it's about you,
with all your values
and deep-rooted expectations.
You thought this would end
differently.
And in a perfect universe,
it would have.
But someone once told me
that the only thing
that can hurt us in life
is the voice
of our own conscience
telling us a story
about right and wrong.
If you turn your head
just right into the wind,
you can make that voice
go down to a whisper.
And after a while,
you might never hear it at all.
[GATE SLAMS]
FEMALE CHORUS:
♪ Hey, hey, dee-dee ♪
♪ Take me back to Piauí ♪
MALE SINGER: ♪ Everybody ♪
FEMALE CHORUS:
♪ Hey, hey, dee-dee ♪
♪ Take me back to Piauí ♪
MALE SINGER:
♪ Hey, hey, dee-dee ♪
- ♪ Take me back to Piauí ♪
- ♪ Hey, hey, dee-dee ♪
MALE SINGER:
♪ Adeus, Paris tropical ♪
♪ Adeus, Brigitte Bardot ♪
♪ O champanhe me fez mal ♪
♪ Caviar já me enjoou ♪
♪ Simonal que estava certo ♪
♪ Na razão do Patropi ♪
♪ Eu também que sou esperto ♪
♪ Vou viver no Piauí ♪
[INSTRUMENTAL BREAK PLAYING]
FEMALE CHORUS:
♪ Hey, hey, dee-dee ♪
♪ Take me back to Piauí ♪
MALE SINGER:
♪ Everybody ♪
FEMALE CHORUS:
♪ Hey, hey, dee-dee
♪ Take me back to Piauí ♪
♪ Hey, hey, dee-dee ♪
MALE SINGER:
- ♪ Take me back to Piauí ♪
♪ Hey, hey, dee-dee ♪
MALE SINGER:
♪ Meu Deus, meu Deus
♪ Take me back to Piauí ♪
FEMALE CHORUS:
♪ Hey, hey, dee-dee ♪
♪ Take me back to Piauí ♪
♪ Hey, hey, dee-dee... ♪
[EXHILARATING MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC CONCLUDES]
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC FADES]